students3k.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy

At Students3k ([www.students3k.com](http://students3k.com/)), the privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

We are not responsible for republished content from this website on other blogs or websites without our permission.

This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Log Files**

We use log files like many other websites. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

**2\. Cookies**

We use cookies to store information about visitor preferences and to record user-specific information on visits and pages the user views so as to provide a custom experience. In regard to third-party advertisers, Students3k has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings.  
****

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on Students3k. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy.  
**3\. Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from Students3k. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

This privacy policy is subject to change with or without notice. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@students3k.com.

**Last Updated: August 10, 2012**
